Buffalo Public School 22 records
Buffalo History Museum. Research Library
Buffalo Public School 22 records
1922 - 1979
1922 - 1962
2 boxes (1.0 linear ft.)
Buffalo (N.Y.) Public School 22
The Buffalo History Museum 1 Museum Court Buffalo, NY 14216 Phone: 716-873-9644 ext. 306 Fax: 716-873-8754 Email: library@buffalohistory.org URI: http://www.buffalohistory.org
Education Parent participation; Public schools New York (State) Buffalo; reminiscences; scrapbooks
Researchers wishing to access this collection must apply for a Scholar Pass and present valid photo ID upon arrival to the library.
Public School 22 originally was located at 2833 Main St., but moved in 1920 to Huntington Ave. near Beard Ave. The school was closed ca. 1981.
Notebook of Mother's Club, 1922-1927; treasurer's notebook, minute books, and scrapbook of the Parent-Teachers Association, 1925-1941; inventory of Department of Industrial Arts, 1935-1948; minute books of Hospitality Club, 1949-1962; guest book pages, 1979; lists of Ketchum Medal winners, 1927-1947; and several reminiscences, ca. 1971.
Organized by format into two series: I. Notebooks. II. Other materials. Chronological arrangement within series.
- Vol. 1: Mother’s Club Notebook, School Number 22, September 19, 1922-May 17, 1927
- Vol. 2: Treasurer’s Notebook, Parent Teacher’s Association, School 22, May 5, 1925-1936
- Vol. 3: Treasurer’s Notebook, Parent Teacher’s Association, School 22, April 8, 1936-April, 1939
- Vol. 4: Secretary’s Minutes, Parent Teacher’s Association, School 22, October 1929-October 11, 1936
- Vol. 5: Secretary’s Minutes, Parent Teacher’s Association, School 22, 1936-1940
- Vol. 6: Shop Inventory, Department of Industrial Arts, Board of Education, 1935-1948
- Vol. 7: Scrapbook, Parent Teacher’s Association, School 22, September 21, 1938-November 1941
- Vol. 8: Hospitality Club, School 22, Minute Book, October 26, 1949-January 20, 1954
- Vol. 9: Hospitality Club, School 22, Minute Book, February 24, 1954-May 21, 1955
- Vol. 10: Hospitality Club, School 22, Minute Book, September 1955-June 1958
- Vol. 11: Hospitality Club, School 22, Minute Book, 1958-1962
- Vol. 12: Guest Book, School 22, June 13, 1979-November 5, 1979
- Folder 1: Ketchum Medal Winners, Public School 22, June 23, 1927-June 1947
- Folder 2: Miscellaneous, includes Reminiscences, 1895-1901